Again? The Mysterious Transfer Student
What?!
Deep Bite was stolen?
By Soleil?
Yeah...
Jun, were you just standing around stunned by her good looks or something?
I'd never do something like that...
I'm not so sure about that...
You told me that she stole Phantom Hornet before you could seal her, too!
And to think Vance and I chased her all that way to find where she was hiding...!
What were you doing, Jun?!
I let my guard down. But no one could've expected it to turn out the way it did!
How will I explain this to Rock Crush and Glober?
What?! Deep Bite was stolen? What do you mean by that, Jun?! (FX-italic)
He got kidnapped?! Oh no! (FX-italic)
Some friend you are! (FX-italic)
That jerk.... Next time I see her, I won't let her off the hook!
Now now, children. Sit down, please.
As I told you before, we have a new transfer student today.
That was today?
Isn't this an unusual time to transfer schools?
Soleil. Nice to meet you. My favorite food is donuts.
Let's give her a round of applause, everyone!
Give me back Deep Bite!
I decline.
(How dare she transfer here!)
Incredible...
She's almost like a pro player!
(That Soleil jerk... Why did she transfer to my school?)
Gimme the ball!
Listen, I'm gonna throw it to her as hard as I can! And while she's distracted, you grab her Metal Breath.
Yeah! Let's get your friend and Phantom Hornet back from that girl!
What is this all of a sudden??
Heads up!
No way...
I heard what you said. If you want it that badly... why not pick it up yourself?
Sigh. It's no use.
Only the chosen one can wield the Metal Breath.
What?!
Tell us that sooner!
Sigh...
Looks like Soleil has no intention of giving Deep Bite back.
What should we do, Jun?
Hmm...
Trouble in paradise?
Vera?
Don't you wanna know where the transfer student lives? I managed to figure it out.
Really?!
Way to go, Vera! You're pretty good at plotting schemes like this!
Choose your words wisely or I'll smack you.
This is...
...the apartment where Crest lives!
Looks like Soleil lives in the same building.
No wonder she looked like a rich family's daughter.
Not only are the addresses the same, but the apartment numbers are the same, too. Which is the top floor!
What?!
Just call them already!
Uh... They might not want to meet with us if we showed up unexpectedly.
But we came all the way here.
[I've been waiting for you. Come on in.]
Welcome, everyone.
Uh.... Who are you?
Who do you think? Nice to meet you. I'm Soleil's mother.
Mother?!
Don't just stand there. Make yourself at home.
E-excuse us...
My son told me many things about you guys.
Your... son?
Are you... perhaps talking about Crest?
That's right.
That means Soleil is...
Oh my, silly Soleil. Didn't she tell you? She's Crest's little twin sister.
THEY'RE TWINS?!
Now that you mention it, they do look kinda similar...
A-are you by any chance Dr. Rhea Cayenne, the leading authority on robotics?
You know me? Well, it's a pleasure.
It-it's an honor to meet you in person!
The feeling's mutual. Especially...
Jun. I've been waiting for the day I'd finally get to meet you.
M-Me?
I've been watching you and those beautiful Metal Cardbots you have.
Ah... heh heh. Have you?
I have so many questions to ask you!
First of all, about your partner...
Ah, you mean Blue Cop? He's right here.
Greetings.
OH MY GOSH!! I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M FINALLY MEETING YOU!!
Ahem. Hello, Blue Cop. I'd like to start by asking how the two of you first met-
Why are you here?
Wha- Ah! You!
Your classmates have come all this way to hang out with you. Why don't you greet them with a happy smile?
Yes, mother.
If I may ask, how much do you know about Soleil and her-
She knows everything.
Things about the Wild Cardbots as well?
Obviously.
These two were the first people I met when I arrived on this planet.
They welcomed me warmly, and took care of me when I was battered and bruised.
Hmph! I didn't know that Wild Cardbots liked to be so spoiled!
Don't you mouth off like that! I'm working with Soleil to serve as a bridge between the humans on this planet and the Wild Cardbots!
You call yourself the bridge, and yet you attack Jun?!
C-calm down...
A bridge between the humans and the Wild Cardbots...
I can't believe it! Sentient robotic lifeforms are having a chat right in front of me!
Mother...
My, how rude of me! I'm sorry. Please continue.
Soleil. Don't you think we can work together better than this?
Meaning?
I'm saying we should join forces to help our friends from planet Machina, whether they're Metal Cardbots or Wild Cardbots.
Crest is currently working hard to develop a vaccine for the Beast Virus.
Is he now?
When the vaccine is completed, Wild Cardbots will no longer be a threat.
Really? I'm proud of him.
You're making it sound so easy.
What do you mean...?
There are countless Wild Cardbots that have escaped from planet Machina.
I don't know how many of them have made it here, but do you really think you can handle them all?
Jun and our people have overcome countless adversaries. This time is no different.
Ahaha... Who could be calling me... Yes, Mr. Mayor?
Dad?
How can I help...
A Wild Cardbot?!
That tank was found on the outskirts of the city. Stop it before it causes any more trouble!
Let's go, Blue Cop!
Roger!
We should go too, Blaion.
Right.
Alright! We're going too!
Let's go catch us that scoop!
Sebastian?
My name is Garrison. I just baked some muffins. Why don't you try some?
They're delicious!
What, is this weak stuff all they got here? I need me some thick oil. Thick!
Man, those guys again? He-hey, if this goes on, I might start getting attached to them!
Tigun! How many times do we have to tell you not to cause any more trouble?
Hmph! You still haven't realized that words won't work on him?
I'm aware.
Grrr... Looks like you guys really want to stop me. Well, I'm always up for a fight!
Let's work together, Soleil.
No. Let's make it a competition to see who can seal him first.
What did you say?
Phantom Hornet. Set Up.
Operation: Disruption. Phantom Legion!
Let's start with a little sting!
You annoying bug! Buzz off! Off!
Soleil! I don't want to compete with you!
That means I win.
Jun, we need to stay calm.
I'll help you fight them, Jun!
Okay. Phoenix Fire! Set Up!
Let's go with the same strategy as last time. Slam Tigun to the ground!
Alright!
Deep Bite. Stop him.
What? B-behind you!
Deep Bite... you're...!
Deep Bite. Set Up.
I knew it! You were on the Wild Cardbots' side all along!
Stop it! This is no time for comrades to be fighting each other!
Comrades? He's clearly the enemy right now!
Please stop, Deep Bite! Come back to us!
Forgive me, Jun! I have no choice but to follow Soleil's orders!
How can you say something like that?!
Jun. Don't you remember? Those sealed within the Metal Breath cannot disobey their master's commands. I know I told you this before.
You mean, you weren't just saying that so I wouldn't worry? Then does that mean he only listened to me because...
Beam Trident Gatling!
The absolute power of Deus Machina, which controls the Metal Cardbot's combat capabilities for the sake of order-
Blaion, take care of Tigun.
Alright.
That very power inside the Metal Breath was the whole reason everyone didn't take kindly to it.
But... But I never...!
Jun! You never used that power.
Even though we solved all sorts of problems through fighting, you still called us your friend from the bottom of your heart.
Deep Bite!
Jun. I cannot follow your commands anymore!
I already called you my friend! And I never give up on my friends!
Didja see that?! Only the strongest coulda' pulled that off!
Looks like he's not just a simple glutton after all.
What's taking you so long, Deep Bite?! Get rid of them quickly!
Be quiet...!
It's okay, Deep Bite! Fight as much as you'd like!
Phoenix Fire! Charge towards Tigun!
Okay! Oh, uh- what?!
Jun, we'll talk about this later!
Don't let him get away, Deep Bite-
Yeah! Hit 'em with Beam Trident!!
A-Alright! Beam Trident!
See that? Even if he was sealed by someone else, we're still connected by our hearts!
What?!
Y-yeah. That's right! Huh? Then who's orders am I supposed to listen to?
Brrrrr! It's cold!
And here I was, just getting heated up!
Blaion. Set Up.
Tiger! Cannonade!
Grrrrrhahahaha!!
Phoenix Fire!
BRRGHH!! Not the squirt gun again!
Blue Cop! Set Up!
Wolf Howl...
Shot!
Dang it!
Huh?!
Don't play with fire!
T-there's no way I'd lose to that. I'm the strongest there is!
Growl... Axe Tooth!
Thunder Howl...
Smash!!
Grrrhaha... That was fun...
Got you this time for sure!
Wild Cardbot! Change Up!
Tigun! Sealed!
Whew. Finally sealed him.
Deep Bite! Soleil lost the competition! All because of your inexplicable behavior!
That's enough, Blaion.
Wha... But...!
I'll give him back to you.
...Why?
You won today. But I won't lose next time.
Soleil! Why do we have to fight? I know we can get along!
Isn't that just your own selfish delusion?
I won't give up on you!
It's going to be awkward at school.
You don't have to tell me that...